Ms. Wang,
please make an exception.
Yeah, Ms. Wang,
please.
You're the best.
Ms. Wang,
please help us.
Our show
is definitely unique.
I'm really sorry.
There are just too many
performances this time.
We have to close the sign-up early.
Zhou Yang,
you know the situation.
Ms. Wang,
with so many performances, there must be many similar ones.
We're a band, we're unique.
Can you
squeeze us in?
I'm really at my wit's end.
Because
the director has already taken away
the application form.
If you really want to do this,
you can go ask him.
Zhou Yang.
Thank you. I'm leaving.
Submarine?
It's no use negotiating with him.
Senior Li Haoyu.
Chen Song.
You remember me?
Of course.
He stands in the sunset,
his shadow so long
that it can't reach yesterday's self.
What the hell is this?
So cheesy.
You wrote scripts for the Drama Club?
Who would want to perform your stuff?
Please.
I beg you.
Give it back to me.
Please give it back to me.
If you want it back,
you have to perform a scene for us first.
Perform a scene.
Do you want it back or not?
Perform a scene. Come on.
How about I perform for you three?
Perform.
Yu, we were just kidding around.
Just kidding around.
Do you find it fun?
Did you see that?
He doesn't think it's fun.
How about you three
perform a scene for us?
I'm sorry.
Say sorry to me.
Sorry.
Louder.
Anything else?
Go, go, go.
Are you in the Drama Club?
Not yet.
But
I want to join it.
Just do it.
I just read your script.
It's quite good.
Believe in yourself.
Keep it up.
By the way,
if anyone
bullies you again,
just say you're with me.
What's your name?
Chen Song.
East ear Chen, Song as in song.
Chen Song, I'll remember you.
Let's go.
Good for you, Chen Song.
You're the president of the Drama Club.
Actually, it's because
there are fewer and fewer members in the club.
And it takes a long time
to prepare a stage.
The school provides little funds.
It's hard to get credits.
So no one
don't want to participate.
So,
did you sign up
for the arts festival?
Yes,
but
maybe we won't perform.
What happened?
Did someone bully you?
I wrote a script,
but
every actor has an opinion.
I can't finish the revision.
Do you think
their opinions make sense?
I... I don't know.
I just hope
every actor is satisfied.
How is that possible?
Your script.
You should listen to yourself.
If it's not good enough,
no one will want to perform.
How many actors do you still need?
Many.
I have an idea.
Director.
Here.
The registration form is filled out.
After much consideration,
I've decided not to participate
in the Olympiad this year.
I hope you understand.
Zhou Yang is too busy to manage.
You couldn't convince him?
Then tell me,
what about Yibei's
olympiad results this year?
Have you thought about it?
I think about it every day.
Because of this,
I...
I lost a lot of hair.
Look.
You can see that
I have less hair.
I can buy you a bottle of hair tonic.
Is that the point?
My boy.
Bin Yan
You always say you have something to do.
I just want to know
what is so important
to make you miss the Olympiad?
Is it the Basketball Club?
If you think the Basketball Club
is taking up your time,
you can quit it.
Director
Come in.
Can you?
What's up?
This is the new program list for the Arts Festival.
Please take a look.
I need to think about it.
Previously,
due to too many applications,
the student union rejected many programs.
Later, the Basketball Club and the Drama Club
proposed to create together,
which opened up our minds.
Finally, many programs
were cooperated.
This year's Arts Festival,
we've got more students
and performances
on stage.
I'm sure it's gonna be awesome.
Basketball Club again?
You've been
making waves lately.
Zhou Yang,
it's great
that you're doing well in basketball,
but remember,
study is always the top priority.
Got it?
You're right.
That's why I'm here today
to submit my application.
I've decided to join this year's Olympiad.
What?
Good, good.
Zhou Yang, let me tell you,
with you on board,
Yibei has a real shot this year.
I'll be going now, sir.
Okay.
Great!
We're all set now!
All set!
Sir, I've decided to join the Olympiad.
Sir, I'll be going now.
You...
My words carry weight.
Zhou Yang,
didn't you say
you're not taking part in the Olympiad this year?
It's just a competition.
It doesn't take much effort.
We two are a team in the Olympiad.
We can maximize efficiency.
It won't affect your stay in the team.
You have the student union
and the basketball team.
And you still have to take part in the Olympiad.
You're really hard-working.
It's just a competition.
It doesn't take much effort.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Hello, hello.
You two
must be Lin Qingyuan's parents, right?
How do you know?
I'm Gu Chenyang's mother.
He said
I would sit with you.
Hello, Chenyang's mom.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome to
Yibei Middle School.
We uphold the core education concept
of simultaneous development of five aspects
to encourage every child to shine.
Of course,
this wouldn't be possible without the
support of higher authorities for private education.
I hope everyone
will capture more of our children's
precious moments
and spread the spirit
of our Yibei students.
Thank you.
Thank you all for your hard work.
Let's get ready to start.
Ready to start.
Okay.
Director.
Mom, just focus on your work.
The entire performance will be recorded.
I'll show you later.
I can't be there to see your performance.
I still feel
a bit regretful.
I'm sorry, son.
It's okay.
It's work, after all.
Auntie, don't be sad.
If it's really not okay,
we'll perform for you again.
Auntie,
my mom brought a camera.
I'll send you the photos later.
Auntie, and me too.
I'll definitely take lots of photos.
Okay, okay.
Thank you all.
Okay, we'll let you go.
Have a safe trip.
Thank you, and good luck
with your performance.
Thank you.
I'm hanging up now. Bye.
Bye.
Where's Li Haoyu?
I haven't seen him.
Make way for your prince!
So cool, Your Highness.
Definitely.
Now that we're all here,
let's take a group photo
to send to Zhou Yang's mom.
Sure.
Sure, come on.
Come on.
Give me a V.
V.
So gorgeous.
Not bad, kids.
Basketball Club and Drama Club, get ready.
You're next.
Come on!
Okay.
Thank you, Mr. Wang. Come on!
Seniors, have you memorized the lines?
Just a few lines.
I've memorized them long ago.
You can just look forward to
my wonderful performance
today.
The next program
is a creative stage play
brought by the Drama Club and the Basketball Club,
The Thorn Prince.
My son is coming.
The sons are coming.
Take good pictures.
It's up to you.
Of course.
Come on.
I heard that the leading actor of this show
is Li Haoyu.
Yeah.
I heard that they've been rehearsing for a long time.
Your Highness.
Stop messing around.
Your ball is about to start.
What ball?
I'm not going to take part in it.
This is your coming-of-age ball.
Come on.
Prince.
Your Majesty.
Royal Father.
Prince.
If you keep making trouble like this,
I will no longer satisfy
any of your demands.
You fool,
what are you waiting for?
Put the crown on me!
Why am I always the one who gets hurt?
He's a pretty good prince.
Yeah, yeah.
He's got a knack for acting.
These are the same gifts every year.
Celebrating with you lot
is such a waste of time.
Get out! All of you!
How dare you!
Your Highness
Your best friend is here.
The Dala Knight has arrived.
Bring him up.
Welcome the Dala Knight.
Come on.
Your Majesty
Your Highness.
Dala Knight.
What birthday gift
have you prepared
for me this time?
Sorry, Your Highness.
I didn't prepare a gift for you.
What's going on?
How come there's no gift?
The script is well written.
Keep it up, Shuang.
Keep an eye on him.
Okay, Mr. Wang.
Your Highness
I saw everything
you did just now.
I don't want to be friends
with a rude person like you.
So
I won't go to
tonight's ball.
Goodbye.
What?
Why did they all leave?
What's going on?
My child.
I'm
so disappointed in you.
Prince.
Please be alone for a while.
Help!
Why is it different from the script?
What should I do now?
Is this Li Haoyu's monologue?
Why is he alone?
Is this part of the design?
Maybe, let's see.
Did he forget his lines?
What's going on?
What was Li Haoyu doing?
When he was on stage,
he held my hand.
I could tell
he didn't know what was going on.
Could it be
that he really forgot his lines?
It's all my fault.
I insisted on changing the script at the last minute.
Is it possible
that he hasn't even seen it?
he didn't know there was a new script?
[The final script has been sent.]
[Please check it.]
[Got it. Thanks.]
[Everyone,]
[make sure to memorize the new lines before bed.]
[Got it. Thanks.]
[Got it. Thanks, President.]
What are you doing?
Gu Chenyang,
What are you doing with the microphone?
Help him finish this act.
Thorn Prince,
now everyone has left you.
How do you feel?
Who?
Who is speaking?
I am your inner demon.
I have everything I want.
I can do whatever I want.
How could there be an inner demon?
Then why didn't you
like the gold and silver
of the princes
but only wanted
the gift of Dala Knight?
That's because
Dala Knight is my good friend.
You need a friend.
They're good at turning the tables.
Yeah.
I...
I don't need it.
I can live freely
on my own.
Are you
free now?
You always pretend to be unconcerned,
putting up thorns to reject the whole world,
thinking that
you won't get hurt.
I don't.
You still think
everyone will leave you in the end.
The only one you can rely on
is yourself.
Am I wrong?
As long as I am strong enough,
I don't need anyone.
Now,
do you still think so?
Although
I didn't write a single line of dialogue,
I still feel so touched.
The seniors are so amazing.
Answer me.
Do you still think so now?
In the universe,
I like pulsars the most.
Pulsar
is a star
that looks very cool,
But actually,
they are very desolate
and lonely.
Because there are no other stars
that can get close.
For a long time,
I was such a star.
But
it's not that I can't be approached,
it's that I
actively distanced myself from the star clusters.
I was afraid to be approached,
and afraid to be abandoned,
so I chose
to abandon the universe.
But now,
everything has changed.
Now,
I have found
my partner.
The pulsar
is no longer lonely,
but us
shining together.
As long as we are together,
we can rock the universe.
They are so excellent.
Yeah.
I really admire them.
I'm so proud.
Next,
let me introduce
our band,
Pulsar Band.
Keyboard, Gu Chenyang.
Bass, Lin Qingyuan.
Thank you.
Guitar, Zhou Yang.
Drummer, Li Haoyu.
And our guest,
violin,
Fu Binyan.
And our script writer,
Chen Song.
Go.
Thank you all for coming to see
our performance this time.
Now,
let's shout out
our name again.
We are
Pulsar Band.